Guide to the Robin Morgan Papers, 1940s-2010 and undated, bulk 1970-2000
Robin Morgan papers 1940s-2010 and undated, bulk 1970-2000
- Writings Series, 1940s-2002 and undated
  - Sisterhood is Global Subseries, 1978-1997 and undated
    - Contributors (Box W16)
      - Park, Sun Chun (South Korea), 1981-1982 and undated
      - Pietila, Hilkka (Finland), 1980-1986 and undated
      - Pineda, Magaly (Spanish speaking Caribbean), 1981-1986 and undated
      - Pintasilgo, Maria de Lourdes (Portugal), 1979-1985 and undated, (2 folders)
      - Portugal, Ana Maria (Peru), 1981-1982 and undated
      - Prado, Danda (Brazil), 1979-1985 and undated
      - Quan, Stella (Guatemala), 1982-1984 and undated
      - Rivero, Isel (Cuba), 1980-1981 and undated
    - Contributors (Box W17)
      - Rowley, Maggie and Beatie Hofmeyr (South Africa), 1981-1982 and undated
      - el Saadawi, Nawal (Egypt), 1979-1983 and undated, (2 folders)
      - Sanchez, Luz Helena (Colombia), 1981-1983 and undated
      - Savane, Marie A. (Senegal), 1981-1984 and undated
      - Schlaffer, Edit and C. Benard (Austria), 1981-1983 and undated
      - Sebestyen, Amanda (England), 1981-1986
      - Sumbung, Titi (Indonesia), 1982-1983 and undated
      - Titkow, Anna (Poland), 1981-1983 and undated
      - Vammen, Tinne (Denmark), 1982-1984 and undated
      - Vajrathon, Mallica (Thailand), 1981-1982 and undated
      - Wali, S. (Afganistan), 1981-1984 and undated
    - Contributors (Box W18)
      - Waring, Marilyn and Ngahuia Te Awekotuku (New Zealand), 1981-1984 and undated
      - Yoha Bagbeni Assumani Ussu (Zaire), 1982 and undated
      - Zaccaria, Paola (Italy), 1982-1986 and undated
      - de Zelaya, Merea Lourdes Centeno (Nicaragua), 1981-1985 and undated
    - Reactions, 1984-1985 and undated
    - Press and reviews, 1980s, (2 folders)
  - Sisterhood is Powerful Subseries, 1969-2000 and undated
    - Random House correspondence (Production, precis, contract, titles, etc.), 1969-1970 and undated (Box W18)
    - Contributors' correspondence, miscellaneous correspondence, 1969-1977 and undated
    - Correspondence re: publicity and promotion, 1969-1970 and undated
    - Foreign rights, 1970-1976
    - Requests, 1971-1974 and undated, (1 of 3 folders)
    - Requests, 1971-1974 and undated, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box W19)
    - General, 1971-1974, (2 folders)
    - Contracts and royalty statements, 1973-2000 and undated
    - Inc. Tax, Inc. dissolution, 1971-1976 and undated, (2 folders)
    - Lawsuit
      - C. Cisler court action, 1973-1974 and undated
      - Fundraising re: court, 1974-1975 and undated
      - Support re: Cisler case, 1974-1978 and undated
    - Reviews and press, 1970-1972 and undated
    - Report, 1974-1976 and undated (Box W20)
    - 30th anniversary edition, 1999-2000 and undated
  - Poems Subseries, 1946-1999 and undated
    - 1946-1958 and undated:Juvenilia
    - 1950s-1960s: Drafts and variants
    - 1965-1972: Drafts and variants
    - 1977 and undated: Drafts and variants
    - 1980:Drafts
    - 1985 Oct.:"Balefire," "Flying South"
    - 1985 Oct.: "Piecing"
    - 1997:"The Spirit Cellar"
    - 1998 Feb.:"Add-Water Instant Blues" (Box W21)
    - 1998 Summer:"Referred Pain"
    - 1998 Oct.:"Learning Clock Patience"
    - 1998:"Treesitter"
    - 1999 Mar.:"Fair Game," "The Last Time"
    - 1999 May:"Count Down"
    - 1999 Spring:"Invocation"
    - 1999 June:"Samizdat," "Universal Donor"
    - 1999 June/July:"Acrobats and Clowns"
    - 1999 July:"Country Matters," "The Farmer's Wife," "The Butcher's Daughter"
    - 1999 Summer:"Fixed Canon"
    - undated:Drafts, (2 folders)
    - undated:Drafts II, (1-2 of 3 folders)
    - undated:Drafts II, (3 of folders) (Box W22)
    - undated: Monster (Early versions: War Games [I and II], home master, master copy manuscript for printer), (2 folders)
    - undated:Unrevised poems in draft for Monster
  - Other Writings by Morgan Subseries, 1940s-2001 and undated, bulk 1970-2001
    - 1940s-1960s:Short stories, (2 folders) (Box W22)
    - 1953, 1955:Juvenilia
    - 1961 and undated:Juvenilia [includes Their Own Country]
    - 1963-1964:Reader's reports for Sterling Lord Publishing
    - 1960s: Poems translated from the Vietnamese
    - 1960s-1970s: Sex and Revolution (collaboration of Morgan and Pitchford) (Box W23)
    - 1978 Feb. 28:Vietnamese poems (translation, NYU reading)
    - 1970s:Drafts of articles, (2 folders)
    - 1970 and undated: Ms. pieces and memos, (2 folders)
    - 1970s:Reactions to Morgan's writings, (2 folders)
    - 1970s-1980s and undated:Comments on others
    - 1970s-1980s and undated:Short articles for Ms.
    - 1970s-1980s: Blurbs, comments, and advice on women's books, A-W, (10 folders) (Box W24)
    - 1981: Death Benefits Chapbook
    - 1989 and undated:UNDP book on HIV/AIDS (Box W25)
    - 1980s:Short Ms. pieces
    - 1980s:Past World columns
    - 1991:Satire on editorial job
    - 1993-1996 and undated:Overview of U.S. feminism for Reader's Companion to U.S. Women
    - 1999:"Human Here Inside of Me"
    - [19-]:Short articles and correspondence, (2 folders)
    - 2000-2001 and undated: Madame Bovary Foreword
    - undated: Their Own Country
    - undated: The Duel
    - undated: The White Haired Witch Draft, (1 of 2 folders)
    - undated: The White Haired Witch Draft, (2 of 2 folders) (Box W26)
  - Writings by Others Subseries, 1964-1970, 1973, 1990s and undated
    - 1964-1970 and undated:Poetry and correspondence for Motive Issue (Box W26)
    - 1973, 1994 and undated:Dissertation and criticism of Morgan
    - 1990s:Wagner, Jane (with comments by Morgan and Tomlin)
  - Grants Subseries, 1970s-1980s
    - 1970s-1980s:Writing grants (Box W26)
    - 1970s-1980s:National Endowment for the Arts
    - 1980s:Guggenheim grant
- Speeches and Interviews Series, 1966-1993 and undated
  Approximately one third of the series consists of drafts of Morgan's speeches; interviews of Morgan by Dorothy Dinnerstein,; Chai Lin and Helen Cooper; and material about her joint poetry tour with Kenneth Pitchford. The remaining two thirds of the material is documents related to Morgan's speeches and interviews (chiefly correspondence, schedules, and contracts). All material is in alphabetical order. Several announcements of Morgan's speeches are located in the Oversize Material at the end of the collection.
  - Appearance requests, 1973-1980, (2 folders) (Box SP1)
  - Joint poetry tour with Kenneth Pitchford, 1966
  - Lectures and readings, 1971-1974, (6 folders)
  - Lectures and readings, 1975-1980, (9 folders) (Box SP2)
  - Lectures and readings, 1981, 1987, (2 folders) (Box SP3)
  - Meredith lecture, 1992
  - Morgan-Chai Lin interview, undated
  - Morgan-Cooper interview, 1981
  - Morgan-Dinnerstein dialogue, 1977-1978 and undated
  - Philadelphia speech and revolt, 1973
  - Speaking engagements and schedule, 1992-1993
- Subject Files Series, 1968-2000 and undated
  The Subject Files Series is organized into five subseries. Apart from the International Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries, which is organized by continents, all material within individual subseries is in alphabetical order. Formats include newspaper clippings, ephemeral publications, short articles, and official letters and documents.
  The General Subseries includes documentation about a controversial plagiarism case involving Robin Morgan, as well as material documenting Morgan's service with Hands Across America. The International Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries documents feminist activism all over the world. The most substantial material comes from South Africa and the Middle East, where Morgan spent months in the Palestinian refugee camps. The Ms. Subseries contains minutes and memos from editorial meetings, information about distribution, and some correspondence with readers. A large portion of the subseries comes from the years when Morgan acted as editor-in chief (1989-1993) and re-launched the magazine as an international bimonthly free of advertising. There is also material concerning the 1980 issue of Ms. about Russian women and Soviet feminism. The Sisterhood Is Global Institute Subseries contains some annual reports and other institutional documents. Finally, the U.S. Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries consists of subject files that cover a number of topics, including witchcraft, demonstrations against the Miss America Pageant, women's clinics, and anti-pornography campaigns. There are also several documents about feminist conferences in the United States and some material concerning figures such as Gloria Steinem,; Marilyn Waring, and Patricia Hearst. A complete set of issues of Rat magazine was removed from this subseries and is located in the Oversize Materials.
  - General Subseries, 1980s-1996
    - Australian plagiarism controversy, 1995-1996 (Box S1)
    - Hands Across America New York Committee, 1980s, (2 folders)
  - International Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries, 1970-1990s and undated
    - Africa
      - General 1989-1993
      - South Africa
        - Academia, 1990s
        - Cape Town notes, 1990s
        - Clips, 1998
        - Comparative essays, 1998 and undated, (3 folders)
        - Disability, homophobia, women's net, media, 1990s
        - History, 1990s and undated, (2 folders)
    - Africa (Box S2)
      - South Africa
        - KwaZulu Natal, 1990s
        - Law/Lobbying, 1997
        - Local government and GAP, 1990s and undated
        - RSA contacts, 1990s and undated
        - Violence, 1990s, (2 folders)
        - Work, farm, SEWU rural, 1990s
    - Asia
      - China, 1995
      - General, 1990s and undated
      - Philippines, 1990s
    - Europe
      - Bosnia, 1990s, (2 folders)
      - France--Issues of Le Torchon Brule, undated
    - Europe (Box S3)
      - General, 1970-1990s and undated
    - General
      - Fundamentalist conference, 1990s
      - Materials about rape, 1973 and undated
    - Middle East
      - Calls and contacts, 1980s and undated
      - Gaza Strip, 1980s
      - General, 1980s, (3 folders)
      - General data file, 1980s
      - Israel-US Zionist aggressives, 1984-1986 and undated
      - Jordan, 1985-1986 and undated
      - Lebanon, 1980s
      - Palestine
        - General, 1988
        - Intifada, 1988
        - UNDP, 1980s
    - Middle East (Box S4)
      - Palestine
        - UNRWA Data, 1980s, (2 folders)
        - Unsorted, 1980s
        - Various articles, 1980s, (2 folders)
      - Saudi Arabian women drivers' report, undated
      - Syria, 1980s and undated
      - West Bank, 1980s, (2 folders)
    - Pacific
      - General, 1970s-1990s and undated
    - Pacific (Box S5)
      - Marilyn Waring
        - Book accounts, correspondence, critiques, 1985-1987 and undated
        - Correspondence, 1987-1991 and undated
        - Essays book, 1985
        - Funding, 1985-1986 and undated
        - Lectures, 1982-1986 and undated
        - Speeches, 1992 and undated
      - New Zealand action, 1980s and undated
    - South America
      - Brazil, 1980s-1990s
  - Ms. Subseries, 1970s-1990s and undated
    - Alton Productions, 1992 and undated (Box S5)
    - Ancillary sales, 1990s
    - Board of Scholars, 1990s and undated
    - Book club, 1990s
    - Contributing editor, 1970s, (1 of 2 folders)
    - Contributing editor, 1970s, (2 of 2 folders) (Box S6)
    - Contributing editors, 1990s
    - Correspondence with Ms. authors, 1970s-1980s
    - Female genital mutilation controversy, 1980s and undated, (2 folders)
    - Foreign distribution, 1990s
    - Formats, 1990s
    - General, 1970s-1980s
    - General information, 1990 and undated
    - Interns, 1980s and undated, (2 folders)
    - Interns and apprentices, 1980s
    - International Board of Advisors, 1990s
    - International contributing editors' memos, 1990s
    - Inventory Morgan left on leaving Ms., 1993
    - Issue on Russian women (Box S7)
      - Background and clips, 1980s
      - Correspondence, 1980-1981
      - Correspondence with Russian women, 1980s
      - Film project, 1980s
      - Lazarova et al. protests, 1980s
      - Magazine and book rights, 1980
      - Mammonova US trip, 1980s, (3 folders)
      - Ms. copy, 1980
      - Russian language materials, 1980 and undated
      - Samizdat, 1980s, (2 folders)
      - Transcripts, 1980s
    - Lang agreements, 1990s (Box S8)
    - Memos, 1980s
    - Minutes from editorial meetings, 1970s-1980s, (2 folders)
    - Morgan memos as editor, 1990s
    - Morgan memos from New Zealand, 1993
    - O'Shea (dishwashers' strike), 1980s
    - Post Ms. Editorship, 1990s
    - Press coverage, 1990s, (2 folders)
    - Press on Ms., 1991
    - Press on Ms. launch in Australia, 1993
    - Reactions from staff and readers, and Morgan's correspondence with both, 1990s, (1 of 2 folders)
    - Rejections A-F, 1970s-1980s, (3 folders) (Box S9)
    - Rejections H-M, 1970s-1980s, (2 folders)
    - Rejections N-R, 1970s-1980s, (2 folders)
    - Rejections S-Z, 1970s-1980s, (1 of 2 folders)
    - Rejections S-Z, 1970s-1980s, (2 of 2 folders) (Box S10)
    - Responses to re-launched Ms. with Morgan as editor, 1990s
    - Ruth Bower meetings, 1990s
    - Ruth Bower memos, 1990s, (2 folders)
    - Steinem Book complaints, 1992-1993
    - Television project, 1992
    - Unsorted materials, 1990-1994, (3 folders)
  - Sisterhood is Global Institute Subseries, 1980s-1999 and undated
    - Annual Report, 1999 (Box S11)
    - Church Women United Foundation, 1982
    - Conference, 1984, (3 folders)
    - Conference, 1984-1985, (4 folders)
    - Conference confirmation cables, undated
    - Conference materials, 1984
    - Conference responses, 1984 and undated
    - Drafts, participants, 1984 and undated
    - Financial information, 1999
    - Ford Foundation, 1981-1987 and undated, (1 of 2 folders)
    - Ford Foundation, 1981-1987 and undated, (2 of 2 folders) (Box S12)
    - Foundation rejections, 1981-1984 and undated, (2 folders)
    - Funding
      - Alida Brill, 1981-1984 and undated
      - Carnegie, 1981-1982 and undated
      - Methodists, 1982-1983 and undated
    - Funding rejections for SIGI meeting, 1984 and undated, (2 folders)
    - Grants pending, 1983 and undated
    - Grants received, 1982-1989 and undated
    - Grant rejections, 1981-1988 and undated, (2 folders)
    - Institutional Documents (vol. 1), 1999, (3 folders) (Box S13)
    - Institutional Documents (vol. 2), 1999, (3 folders)
    - Invitations: Press conference, 1984
    - Invitations to strategy meeting, 1984 and undated
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1980s-1990s
    - Members A-Z, 1980s-1990s and undated, (1-2 of 7 folders)
    - Members A-Z, 1980s-1990s and undated, (3-7 of 7 folders) (Box S14)
    - Panels, 1984 and undated
    - Participation letter and packet, 1985 and undated
    - Party invitations and list, undated
    - Press conference, 1984
    - Press follow-up, 1984 and undated
    - Press mailing lists undated
    - Shalala Party, 1985 and undated
    - Skaggs Foundation, 1980s, (2 folders)
    - Statement and draft, undated (Box S15)
    - Steering Committee meeting, 1999
    - Strategy meeting, 1984 Nov. 11-16, (6 folders)
    - Transition binder, 1999
  - U.S. Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries, 1968-2000 and undated
    - Conferences
      - de Beauvoir conference, 1979 (Box S15)
      - Canadian conference, 1983
      - Lesbian conference in Los Angeles, 1972-1973, (5 folders)
    - Conferences (Box S16)
      - Wise Women's conference, 1985
    - Controversies
      - Chesler, Phyllis, 1980s
      - Hearst, Patricia, 1980s, (2 folders)
      - Steinem, Gloria
        - 1979
        - 1970s, (2 folders)
        - New Zealand trip controversy, 1977
    - Controversies (Box S17)
      - Swinton Trial (Saxe), 1975-1976 and undated, (2 folders)
    - Demonstrations
      - Miss America, 1968, (2 folders)
      - Miss America, 1969
    - General
      - Anti-porn, 1970s-1980s, (4 folders)
      - Bella Abzug
        - 1977-1979 and undated
    - General (Box S18)
      - Bella Abzug
        - Congressional campaign
          - 1986 and undated
          - 1992 and undated
      - Feminist organizing papers, 1980s-1990s and undated
      - Grove Press action, 1970, (2 folders)
      - Guerrilla Girls, undated
      - Lesbian theory and activism, 1980s
      - Medical self-Help clinics, 1970s
      - NY Women's Rights Center, 1970s and undated
      - Up From Under, 1970-1973, (3 folders)
    - General (Box S19)
      - Web magazine project, 2000
      - Wicca, 1970s and undated, (3 folders)
      - Witch materials, 1968-1972 and undated
      - Women's Studies stuff, 1970s
- Personal Files Series, 1950s-1989 and undated
  Consists primarily of papers related to Robin Morgan's formal education at Columbia University. Formats include class notes, essays, and rather brief notebooks from her trips to the Middle East, Austria and Egypt, further documented in the Photographic and Visual Materials Series and Subject Files Series. Other material includes FBI and CIA files, which Morgan requested through the Freedom of Information Act in the 1970s. Each of the three categories (Education at Columbia University, Trips, and Other Personal) is arranged in chronological order.
  - Education at Columbia University (Box PER1)
    - 1957:Psychology, (2 folders)
    - 1958:Anthropology, (2 folders)
    - 1958:German
    - 1958:Victorian Literature
    - 1958-1959:Renaissance Literature
    - 1959:Art of Poetry
    - 1959:Civilization and Culture
    - 1950s-1960s:Essays and school papers, (2 folders)
  - Education at Columbia University (Box PER2)
    - 1960:English
    - 1960:Exam
  - Trips
    - 1978-1979:Aborted Iran trip
    - 1985-1986 and undated:Mid-East trip maps and itineraries
    - 1989:Palestine/Israel notebook
    - undated:Jerusalem notebook
    - undated:Jordan notebook
    - undated:Vienna and Cairo notebook
  - Other Personal
    - 1962:Apartment lease
    - 1976-1978:FBI and CIA files, (2 folders)
- Teaching Materials Series, 1971-1998 and undated, bulk 1995-1997
  Includes material related to Robin Morgan's position as an adjunct professor at the Union Graduate School; as a visiting chair and guest professor of Women's Studies at New College (Sarasota, Fla.); and as a visiting professor at the University of Denver Graduate School of International Affairs. The bulk comes from the Denver position and includes contracts; course material related both to the courses that Morgan attended and to the courses she taught on feminism; student papers; and teaching-related correspondence. The material is arranged in alphabetical order.
  - New College, Fla. 1971-1972, (4 folders) (Box T1)
  - Union Graduate School, 1974
  - University of Denver
    - Books and references, 1996-1997 and undated, (4 folders)
    - Contacts, 1996-1997 and undated
    - Contracts and original correspondence, 1995-1997
    - Extra curriculum appears, 1997 and undated
    - General, 1996-1998, (1 of 3 folders)
  - University of Denver (Box T2)
    - General, 1996-1998, (2-3 of 3 folders)
    - Graduate course in communications (correspondence), 1996-1997
    - Graduate School International Studies, 1996-1997 and undated
    - Provost lecture, 1997
    - Provost lunch speech, 1997
    - Student papers, 1995-1997
    - Women's Studies, 1996-1997 and undated
- Audio-Visual Materials Series, circa 1985-2001 and undated
  Contains cassette tapes with interviews that Morgan conducted with women in the Middle East during two visits in 1985 and 1989. There is also a recording of Morgan's reading of poems selected from A Hot January as well as a videotape titled, Saturday's Child; A Memoir. The collection is arranged by media type.
  [Originals closed to use. Use copies available in the collection. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
  [Although the contents of the taped interviews are open to research, patrons are responsible for obtaining permission to publish from them.]
  - Cassette Tapes (Originals), circa 1985, 1989 and undated (Box AV1)
    - OR1. UNDP, circa 1985
    - OR2. UNDP, Gaza and the North circa 1985
    - OR3. Health center, Gaza, visits, circa 1985
    - OR4. Vienna brief, Gaza, circa 1985
    - OR5. Jerusalem, Giucamone, circa 1985
    - OR6. Settlements for women, Zahira Kamal, Palestinian women's work, circa 1985
    - OR7. Gaza - Health visits, Y. Barbary, circa 1985
    - OR8. Rita Giacaman, Ramallah, 1989 Jan. 14
    - OR9. End of Ibdn Haddi, Suha Eid, Jordan, circa 1985
    - OR10. Jordan, Haifa Bashur, Irbid, circa 1985
    - OR11. Jordan, Bag'A Camp, start of Haifa Bashur, circa 1985
    - OR12. Irbid, Suf camps, start of Ibdn Haddi, circa 1985
    - OR13. Village coop, Al Arrub camp, 1989
    - OR14. Jalazone camp, village coop, 1989
    - OR15. Gaza, circa 1985
    - OR16. Hayat Yaghi, Amman New camp, circa 1985
    - OR17. Ramallah Women's Teaching College, women's work, undated
  - Videotapes
    - OR18. Women to Women: "Saturday's Child," 2001 Mar.
  - Compact Discs
    - OR19.A Hot January, Selected Readings 1996-1999, 2000
  - Master and Use Copies (Box AV2)
    [Master copies are closed to general use.]
- Photographic and Visual Materials Series, circa 1974, 1982-1995 and undated
  This series includes 240 photographs and two painted portraits.
  - Photographic Materials, 1982-1995
    Consists of 240 photographs, 222 of which are color, and 18 black and white. Most of the images are snapshots from Morgan's trip to Egypt; the rest are pictures of Isel Rivero, and some taken by her. The photographs are arranged in their original order.
    - H Temple and Hathor temple, undated (Box PH1)
    - Valley of Kings and Queens, Hats., temples, goats, undated
    - Nile, pyramids, Nawal, Sphinx, cat, undated
    - N's country house and garden, Nile, undated
    - N's village and chickens, relatives, children, undated
    - Blake at Goodbye Pyramids, undated
    - Bookshop, plane to Lufor, Fairy, Colossus, undated
    - H Temple and Hathor temple, undated
    - Miscellaneous photos, undated
    - Isel Rivero
      - 1982 and undated
      - In Nicaragua, undated
      - In Rwanda and Uganda, 1994-1995 and undated
      - In Namibia, 1989-1990 and undated
  - Visual Materials, circa 1974, undated
    This subseries includes two large painted portraits of Robin Morgan. One is a formal studio pose, painted on wood and depicting Morgan as a young woman during the time that she was a television and radio personality. The other was painted on canvas by Pat Mainardi (author of Politics of Housework) after Morgan achieved fame as a radical feminist activist and poet.
    - Portrait, by Pat Mainardi, oil on canvas, circa 1974 (Oimage 1: Please see catalog record for location.)
    - Portrait, formal studio pose, painted on wood, undated (Oimage 2: Please see catalog record for location.)
- Oversize Materials
  Contains materials from the Writings Series, the Subject Files Series, and the Speeches and Interviews Series. Poetry broadsides include the poem White Night, dedicated to Morgan and signed by Adrienne Rich. The Subject Files Subseries contains a complete set of issues of the feminist magazine Rat. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Writings Series (Box OS1)
    - Depth Perception Subseries
      - Copyright file -- Sojourner, 1978 Aug.
    - Going Too Far Subseries
      - Reviews and adverts, 1977
    - A Hot January Subseries
      - Production, undated
    - Lady of the Beasts Subseries
      - Reviews and adverts, 1976-1978 and undated
    - Poems Subseries
      - Poems broadsides and awards, 1981-1982
  - Subject Files Series
    - International Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries
      - The Middle East -- General, 1980s
    - U.S. Feminist Activism and Resources Subseries
      - Rat magazine, undated, (3 folders)
  - Speeches and Interviews Series
    - Announcements for speaking engagements, 1972-1992 and undated